Guide to the Chancellor of the University of Pittsburgh, J. Dennis O'Connor, Administrative Files, 1991-1995 UA.2.10.1991-1995
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Speeches, 1991-1995; IV.
  - Class of 1943 Dinner, October 1993 (Box 70, Folder 152)
  - Speech to Bradford Campus, November 1, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 153)
  - New York Alumni reception, November 3, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 154)
  - Senate Council, November 15, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 155)
  - Remarks to football recruits, December 3, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 156)
  - Remarks to football recruits, December 11, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 157)
  - Senate Council, February 7, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 158)
  - Board of Trustees meeting, February 17, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 159)
  - Health Care Reform symposium, February 28, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 160)
  - "The Message in the Cornerstone" - Honors Convocation, March 1, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 161)
  - Honors Convocation script, March 1, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 162)
  - Senate Appropriations Committee Hearings, March 9, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 163)
  - Rotary Ethics Symposium, March 16, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 164)
  - Senate Council, March 21, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 165)
  - University Center for International Studies (UCIS) 25th Anniversary, March 28, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 166)
  - Detre Chair announcement, April 8, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 167)
  - Senate Council, April 11, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 168)
  - Administrative & Policy Studies - School of Education, April 12, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 169)
  - Commission on Higher Education 75th Anniversary, April 19, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 170)
  - International 3rd Century Conference, April 20, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Blue and Gold Society induction, April 25, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Distinguished Teaching, Research, and Public Service Awards reception, April 25, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Center for Assistive Technology, April 26, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Europe Business Opportunity Conference, April 26, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Commencement press conference, May 2, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - David McCullough Commencement address, May 2, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Commencement, May 2, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Senate Council, May 9, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Leadership Conference, May 11, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Pitt Ambassadors Scholarship Dinner - Jack Kemp, June 2, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - 30th Congress of the International Institute of Iberoamerican Literature, June 13, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Senate Council, June 13, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Center for the Neural Basis of Cognition, June 13, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Roundtable session, June 16, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Pennsylvania Governor's School for International Studies, June 26, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Dedication of the School of Pharmacy Entrance and Brick Walkway, June 26, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - North Hills slide show - Tuchi script, June 1994 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Board of Trustees meeting, June 30, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - International Association of School Librarianship Conference, July 18, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - "Thoughts on Tradition" for Pitt News, August 8, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Freshman Convocation, August 27, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Panther Kickoff lunch (canceled), August 29, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Dr. Leon Haley recommendation, August 1994 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Lantern Night, September 1, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Tony Dorsett reception, September 2, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - New Faculty Orientation, September 2, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Department of Defense Site Visit - Materials Research Center, September 7, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Senate Council, September 12, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Charge for Senior Vice Chancellor for Health Sciences, September 13, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Corporate Leadership Council meeting, September 15, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 31)
  - Flight 427 Memorial Service, September 19, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 32)
  - DePaul University Distinguished Alumni Awards, September 18, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 33)
  - Alumni - GSPIA reception, September 20, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 34)
  - Urban League of Pittsburgh 76th Annual Meeting - Introduction for Hugh Price, September 21, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 35)
  - Chancellor's Circle reception, September 24, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 36)
  - Column for William Pitt Journal, October 12, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 37)
  - Reunion of a Decade reception, October 13, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 38)
  - "Forging a New Freedom" Breakfast, October 13, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 39)
  - Pitt Lettermen reception, October 14, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 40)
  - Broadhurst Science Center groundbreaking, October 14, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 41)
  - Remarks for Ambassador van Agt, October 20, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 42)
  - United Way reception, October 27, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 43)
  - Minority Education Conference, October 24, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 44)
  - Remarks for Board of Trustees, October 21, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 45)
  - Message for William Pitt Journal Honor Roll, October 26, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 46)
  - Staff Association Council Fall Assembly, October 31, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  - R. James Woolsey seminar, November 1, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  - Message for Panther Prints yearbook, November 4, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 49)
  - Senate Council, November 9, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 50)
  - Mary Bonach tribute, November 16, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 51)
  - Football stadium groundbreaking, November 18, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 52)
  - Walt Waters retirement party, November 22, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 53)
  - City Planning Commission Hearing on Master Space Plan, November 22, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 54)
  - National Institute of Health site visit, November 28, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 55)
  - The Chancellor's Column - "Entrepreneurial Activities", November 1994 (Box 71, Folder 56)
  - Big Brothers Big Sisters Roast, December 1, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 57)
  - Dedication of Human Energies Lab, December 2, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 58)
  - Reception for Dr. Herberman, December 7, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 59)
  - Senate Council, December 12, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 60)
  - 20-Year Recognition ceremony, December 14, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 61)
  - Dickson Prize, December 15, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 62)
  - Holiday and New Year greeting, December 15, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 63)
  - "The Meaning of Responsibility", December 1994 (Box 71, Folder 64)
  - Southern California Pitt Club reception, January 5, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 65)
  - Wilfried Daehnick reception, January 13, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 66)
  - Pitt Ambassadors luncheon, January 19, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 67)
  - Posthumous degree presented to Eugene Raykin, passenger on Flight 427, February 1, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 68)
  - "A City for the 21st Century", February 7, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 69)
  - Senate Council, February 13, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 70)
  - Board of Trustees meeting, February 16, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 71)
  - Founders Day, February 27, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 72)
  - Sister Rosemary Donley tribute, February 27, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 73)
  - Honors Convocation, February 28, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Luncheon with Brazilian Ambassador Paulo-Tarso Flecha de Lima, March 7, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Honors Admissions Day, March 17, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Senate Council, March 20, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Luncheon with Dr. Edmund Gordon, March 21, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Rotary Ethics Symposium, March 22, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Chancellor's Circle reception, March 23, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - School of Health and Rehabilitation Sciences (SHRS) 25th Anniversary, March 24, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Greek Week Opening Ceremonies, March 30, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Distinguished Teaching, Research, Public Service Awards reception, April 12, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - School of Social Work's "Evening of Recognition", April 29, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Talking points for College of Arts & Sciences students, April 30, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Commencement, April 30, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Dr. George Bernier portrait unveiling, May 12, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Senate Council, May 17, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Somerset Rotary Lunch, May 19, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Law School Commencement, May 26, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - "Highlights at Pitt", June 1, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Modern Language Association of America, "What is the Question?", June 2, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - American Astronomical Society, June 12, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Dickey, McCamey, and Chilcote Chair reception, June 22, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - University Child Development Center ribbon cutting, June 22, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Remarks to the Board of Trustees, June 22, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 23)